

# CONTACT

- 970.846.9720
- joncrides@gmail.com
- 40383 Anchor Way
- www.joncariveau.com

### **EDUCATION**

# 1986-1991 OKLAHOMA STATE UNIVERSITY

- · Bachelor of Science
- Horticulture/Turf Grass
- Business minor

### 1992

### **BARNETT BICYCLE INSTITUTE**

· Comprehensive course

### **SKILLS**

- Project Management
- Public Relations
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking

# **SPECIALITES**

- Word Press
- Social Media
- Shopify
- Klayvio
- · Meta Business Suite

# JON CARIVEAU

# MARKETING/BRAND MANAGER

# **PROFILE**

I am a 30+ year bicycle industry professional that has focused on growing brand, customer loyalty and community. I have been focused on marketing at every level to share brand story through creative digital content and in-person interactions. Having worked hands-on in manufacturing to creating awareness for a high end brand I have strong creative, technical and mechanical background. Content creation to drive interest and customer loyalty, along with serving as face and voice of brand have been my strong passions.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

Moots 2008-PRESENT

Marketing Manager & Social Media/Content Specialist

- Developed and executed comprehensive marketing strategies and campaigns that align with the company's goals and objectives.
- Lead, mentor, and manage a high-performing marketing team, fostering a collaborative and results-driven work environment.
- Monitor brand consistency across marketing channels and materials.
- Maintained and developed content for consistent website updates.
- Managed and maintained Shopify webstore component of overall website.

Moots 2001-2008

Global Sales Director

- Worked one on one with dealership and distributor accounts worldwide, lead a small sales team to meet sales goals and annual growth targets.
- Oversaw market research to identify emerging trends, customer needs, and competitor strategies.
- Monitor brand consistency across marketing channels and materials.

Moots 1997-2000

Hands on manufacuring

- Worked on the production floor as hands-on skilled frame builder.
- First hand knowledge of every aspect of manufacturing bicycle frames.

### REFERENCE

### **Nate Bradley**

Moots/CEO

Phone: 970-879-1676 Email: nateb@moots.com

### Billy Sinkford

**Echos Communications** 

Phone: 415-601-5148

Email: billy@echoscomm.com